<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Source Code on Mark Arneman</title>
    <link>/tags/source-code/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Source Code on Mark Arneman</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/tags/source-code/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Popular Plex</title>
      <link>/projects/popular-plex/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/projects/popular-plex/</guid>
      <description>This script is designed to run weekly, generating collections in Plex of most popular Movies and Television based on the data from the Tautulli API. It uses the python-plexapi package and requests. The idea behind this project was to recreate Netflix&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;What&amp;rsquo;s Popular&amp;rsquo; list View the source code on GitHub </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Docker Compose Files</title>
      <link>/posts/docker-compose/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 17:49:49 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/docker-compose/</guid>
      <description>I created a public GitHub repo to be informational and used as a reference for others when creating and managing multiple docker-compose files with Traefik acting as a reverse proxy.&#xA;I run my containers on an Alpine Linux virtual machine.&#xA;Check it out over on GitHub: https://github.com/bearlikelion/docker-compose&#xA;Containers Container Description Additional BitWarden_rs Password manager Hub Matomo Website Analytics Hub Media Automated media server - Deluge Jackett Radarr Sonarr ReadMe Netdata Performance monitoring Hub Nextcloud A safe home for all your data Hub OpenVPN OpenVPN Server Work in progress Organizr HTPC/Homelab services organizer Hub Pi-hole Network based ad blocker Hub - Website Relay Tor Relay Server Hub Teamspeak Teamspeak 3 Server Hub Traefik Traefik reverse proxy Hub - Docs Warrior Archive Team warrior Hub Watchtower Container auto-updates Hub </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cube3</title>
      <link>/projects/cube3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2019 11:00:49 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/projects/cube3/</guid>
      <description>Play in your browser or download it here! View the high scores online here!&#xA;About Cube3 (Cube Cubed) is a game created for 8 Bits to Infinity&amp;rsquo;s Two Button Jam.&#xA;The player controls a cube left and right across a grid to avoid oncoming obstacles.&#xA;Credits Developed by:&#xA;Mark Arneman Rensei Music By: Mister Hippo Lazer84 font by Sunrise Digital&#xA;High scores provided by Dreamlo&#xA;Contains music ©2019 Joshua McLean licensed under Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Game of Game of Games</title>
      <link>/projects/thegameofgameofgames/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 11:10:44 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/projects/thegameofgameofgames/</guid>
      <description>The Game of Game of Games A game created by Mark Arneman for the #TVGameJam.&#xA;Play in your browser or download it here!&#xA;View the highscores online!&#xA;About The Game of Game of Games is my entry into the #TVGameJam. This was a solo development effort as well as my first released game! It was inspired by the television show, Ellen&amp;rsquo;s Game of Games.&#xA;The project source is available on GitHub​</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
